{"sentences":[{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"gone"},{"correct":true,"text":"been"},{"correct":false,"text":"arrived"},{"correct":false,"text":"come"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have (61).... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"much"},{"correct":false,"text":"few"},{"correct":false,"text":"a little"},{"correct":true,"text":"a lot"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited (62).... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"just"},{"correct":false,"text":"already"},{"correct":true,"text":"yet"},{"correct":false,"text":"never"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen (63).... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":true,"text":"went"},{"correct":false,"text":"saw"},{"correct":false,"text":"got"},{"correct":false,"text":"left"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we (64).... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"where"},{"correct":false,"text":"who"},{"correct":false,"text":"whose"},{"correct":true,"text":"which"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace (65).... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":true,"text":"world"},{"correct":false,"text":"globe"},{"correct":false,"text":"continent"},{"correct":false,"text":"countryside"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the (66).... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"guests"},{"correct":true,"text":"visitors"},{"correct":false,"text":"strangers"},{"correct":false,"text":"neighbours"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so (67).... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"prefer"},{"correct":false,"text":"need"},{"correct":true,"text":"had better"},{"correct":false,"text":"want"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I (68).... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"next"},{"correct":false,"text":"other"},{"correct":false,"text":"new"},{"correct":true,"text":"another"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting (69).... city, so we have to get up early. See you .... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"for"},{"correct":true,"text":"in"},{"correct":false,"text":"after"},{"correct":false,"text":"behind"}],"question":"Dear Demi, Greetings from Beijing. Liz and I have .... in China for a week now. We've already visited .... of interesting places but there's so much we haven't seen .... . Yesterday we .... to the Summer Palace .... is one of the most famous royal gardens in the .... . It is located just outside Beijing and it's really amazing. It's also very well-preserved, so .... can see many of its beautiful features. Well, I .... go and get some rest now. Tomorrow we're visiting .... city, so we have to get up early. See you (70).... a week. All the best, Anna"},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"Besides"},{"correct":false,"text":"What is more"},{"correct":false,"text":"All in all"},{"correct":true,"text":"For example"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. (71)...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"due"},{"correct":true,"text":"as a result"},{"correct":false,"text":"in addition"},{"correct":false,"text":"so that"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" (72).... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":true,"text":"than"},{"correct":false,"text":"to"},{"correct":false,"text":"from"},{"correct":false,"text":"even"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV (73).... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"say"},{"correct":true,"text":"are said"},{"correct":false,"text":"said"},{"correct":false,"text":"were said"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people (74).... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"contact"},{"correct":false,"text":"connection"},{"correct":true,"text":"touch"},{"correct":false,"text":"pace"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in (75).... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"Despite"},{"correct":true,"text":"However"},{"correct":false,"text":"Although"},{"correct":false,"text":"In spite"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. (76).... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"exchanged"},{"correct":false,"text":"removed"},{"correct":false,"text":"overtaken"},{"correct":true,"text":"replaced"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  (77).... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"more"},{"correct":false,"text":"the more"},{"correct":true,"text":"most"},{"correct":false,"text":"the most"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that (78).... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":false,"text":"but"},{"correct":false,"text":"still"},{"correct":true,"text":"as"},{"correct":false,"text":"also"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative (79).... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. .... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."},{"choices":[{"correct":true,"text":"Nevertheless"},{"correct":false,"text":"Regardless"},{"correct":false,"text":"Anyway"},{"correct":false,"text":"Similarly"}],"question":"According to a recent survey, technology has influenced our lives in various ways. ...., more and more people have become \"couch potatoes\" .... of spending more time watching TV .... being with their family or friends. A great number of people .... to use the Internet every day not only for professional reasons but also to keep in .... with friends and relatives. .... , the majority of the people who were interviewed do not believe that books will eventually be  .... by the net. Some people claim that .... changes technology has brought are negative .... it hasn't managed to bring us closer. (80).... , others argue that things may be different but not necessarily worse since change is part of life."}]}

